<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Josh Austin</title>
 <link href="http://josh-austin.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://josh-austin.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-05-30T12:23:34-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://josh-austin.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Joshua Austin</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Why I Love Macbook But Dislike iPhone</title>
   <link href="http://josh-austin.com/2015/05/30/Why-I-Love-Macbook-But-Hate-iPhone/"/>
   <updated>2015-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://josh-austin.com/2015/05/30/Why-I-Love-Macbook-But-Hate-iPhone</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This March I purchased a MacBook Pro 13&amp;quot; and replaced my 1st Generation Moto X with a shiny iPhone 6.  Within 2 months I put my iPhone 6 on eBay and bought a 2nd Generation Moto X.  Why?  Mainly because I prefer the Android operating system and the Moto X&amp;#39;s low-power notification screen display.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a computer geek, I strongly prefer the customizability of Android.  To be fair, if you are seeking an easy-to-use interface then iOS may be a better fit for you.  Additionally I found that I preferred the Moto X&amp;#39;s availability of voice activation on battery over needing to push down the iPhone button to talk to Siri.  Speaking of the button, I also like the Moto X&amp;#39;s display of notifications when waving my hand over it or pulling it out of my pocket.  I know much faster if a notification is important or not because I don&amp;#39;t have to push a button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My MacBook Pro 13&amp;quot;, on the other hand, is the best laptop I&amp;#39;ve had so far.  The OS is Unix-like, which is very helpful for some of my web development, the touch pad and keyboard feel &amp;quot;natural&amp;quot; to me, and, despite being a little on the gimmicky side of marketing (did I invent a new word?), the Retina display is definitely sharp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, I am glad I got my MacBook Pro and I was glad to try out the iPhone and learn the hard way why I like the Moto X so much.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What is love?</title>
   <link href="http://josh-austin.com/2015/05/29/What-Is-Love/"/>
   <updated>2015-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://josh-austin.com/2015/05/29/What-Is-Love</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We always hear of the term &amp;quot;falling in love&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;falling out of love&amp;quot;.  It is very common even within Christian circles for people to assume that love is an emotion: something that happens (like a lightning bolt or a chemistry experiment).  It is perfectly reasonable to reconsider a dating relationship if it is certain one will not be happy if the relationship grows into the lifetime relationship of marriage.  However, many marriages miserably fail because of the assumption that if the associated emotions are missing, then love must be absent, and therefore the lifetime commitment made at the wedding should be reconsidered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeshua the Messiah, who is HaShem Himself, is the embodiment of perfect love and therefore the prime example.  The Messiah provides the perfect, defining example of love.  Ultimately, love is a choice that, while emotions are definitely involved, transcends emotion to commit selflessly to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Yeshua was about to be sacrificed for our sins, he experienced strong emotions that stressed him.  He &lt;em&gt;naturally&lt;/em&gt; did not want to go through with this.  Nobody would.  He pleaded to his Father:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Father, if you are willing, remove this cup from me.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Luke 22:42, ESV&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet he knew what his mission was, let the love for his father and for his creation transcend his feelings, and conceded:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, not my will, but yours, be done.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Luke 22:42, ESV&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even after his concession, and even after an angel ministered to him, he still experienced agony:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there appeared to him an angel from heaven, strengthening him.  And being in an agony he prayed more earnestly; and his sweat became like great drops of blood falling down to the ground.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Luke 22:43-44&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the Messiah still chose to complete his mission, become the perfect sacrifice for our sins, and changed history for the better ever since.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
